{
    "id": "23e2a69212f24f358203a4c9af809103",
    "title": "Phrasal Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I don't want you to bring ........................... that topic again.",
            "description": "To bring up a topic is to mention it.",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "on",
                "up"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "96032ab2172942bea4a75734fd14c0ad"
        },
        {
            "question": "The teacher asked the boy to do the exercise .............................",
            "description": "To do something over is to repeat it.",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "over",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8ba5ba695fd0489391453169afec9680"
        },
        {
            "question": "She filled ................................ the bottle with water.",
            "description": "To fill up a bottle is to fill it to capacity.",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "in",
                "up"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "79f93fed451545cbb922ffa2f46cc241"
        },
        {
            "question": "I found that she had been saying nasty things about me behind my ............................",
            "description": "To do something behind someone's back is to do something without their knowledge.",
            "answers": [
                "head",
                "back"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1d0218dc1b704a34997ba9fca3402526"
        },
        {
            "question": "The restaurant was giving ................................. free food.",
            "description": "To give something away is to give it for free.",
            "answers": [
                "off",
                "away",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "fc38a16521d94525a28e243b39ee594a"
        },
        {
            "question": "When are you going to give me my money .................................?",
            "description": "To give something back is to return it.",
            "answers": [
                "back",
                "again",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1a0f4ceef9764c2db1d2e8117259cd91"
        },
        {
            "question": "Put ............................... your coat before going out.",
            "description": "To put on a coat is to wear it.",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "on",
                "over"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "62cfe66a8ec445fbb67848518e851fae"
        },
        {
            "question": "We use a fire extinguisher to put ............................... fire.",
            "description": "To put out fire is to extinguish it.",
            "answers": [
                "off",
                "out",
                "up"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "85a2627b55d5477a827fa5b222b6a884"
        },
        {
            "question": "Please take ................................ these instructions lest you should forget them.",
            "description": "To take down is to make a written note.",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "off",
                "down"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "8d934cd90bad4095bb2ba7501d87ad41"
        },
        {
            "question": "You must put .................................... some money for your retirement.",
            "description": "To put something away is to save or store it.",
            "answers": [
                "off",
                "away",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0fa4fe44f6754d748bc6ce7746380a96"
        },
        {
            "question": "Although he deserved the job, his application was turned ..............................",
            "description": "To turn something down is to reject it.",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "down",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "fd80522187cd4c34916cd532a0116ee2"
        },
        {
            "question": "We should not throw .................................. anything useful.",
            "description": "To throw something away is to discard it.",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "off",
                "away"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "b96a866ced934b459cb062652f8f9d1e"
        }
    ]
}